Proper golf etiquette is something that every golfer needs to know and practice while out on the golf course.
My name is Jared Garbett and I'm with Echo Farms.
And I'm going to teach you how to practice proper golf etiquette while out on the putting green.
You're going to begin by taking the flag out of the flag stick.
Making sure not to damage the edges of the cup.
Going to gently place the flag stick on the ground making sure not to throw or drop it.
You're then going to check your line of path to walk so that you know you're not in anybody else's way.
Seeing that the path is clear, I can walk over and mark my golf ball.
Whenever I get to my golf ball, I want to take a coin or a ball marker and gently place it behind my golf ball.
Making sure not to move my golf ball.
After marking the ball, you can pick the ball up.
So that anybody else that is behind you is not in the way of your golf ball.
This is how practice proper golf etiquette while on the green.